​​​ ​[sick-ass anime opening]​ ​​
​​​ ​You should rename your thighs to the Gaza Strip yeah​ ​​
​​​ ​Lie down, baby, arch your back now​ ​​
​​​ ​Maybe you can help me get what I want​ ​​
​​​ ​And curve your little spine and tell me that you're mine​ ​​
​​​ ​It's all about the game and what you flaunt​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah, I know that there's no pleasing you​ ​​
​​​ ​When you know that you're not teasin' me​ ​​
​​​ ​She's an absolute terror for absolute territory​ ​​
​​​ ​Hmmm?​ ​​
​​​ ​Somebody–​ ​​
​​​ ​Help me collect extra THICC aSss​ ​​
​​​ ​dа-а​ ​​
​​ ​(yes)​ ​​
​​​ ​let me in...​ ​​
​​​ ​IM COMING FOR THE THIIIIGHS​ ​​
​​​ ​[Laughs Uncontrollably In Russian]​ ​​
​​​ ​Hmmm...​ ​​
​​​ ​Ohhhhh...​ ​​
​​​ ​So,​ ​​
​​​ ​where are the anime boobas?​ ​​
​​​ ​Is that it?​ ​​
​​​ ​I have no idea!​ ​​
​​​ ​[died]​ ​​
​​​ ​well...​ ​​
​​​ ​I think they are here.​ ​​
​​​ ​But...​ ​​
​​​ ​can you even read?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yes, I can!​ ​​
​​​ ​not sure.​ ​​
​​​ ​You are not helping!​ ​​
​​​ ​[door creaks]​ ​​
​​ ​You are not helping!​ ​​
​​ ​Baah, f### you!​ ​​
​​​ ​[door creaks]​ ​​
​​ ​I am trying!​ ​​
​​​ ​I am trying!​ ​​
​​​ ​alright.​ ​​
​​​ ​[ゴゴゴ]​ ​​
​​​ ​[̴̤̎ゴ̴̧̃ゴ̵̹̎ゴ̴̝̔]̵̠̿​ ​​
​​​ ​[door creaking]​ ​​
​​​ ​[thuds]​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh my GOD!​ ​​
​​​ ​WAAH!–​ ​​
​​​ ​nO NO, please!​ ​​
​​​ ​[struggling]​ ​​
​​​ ​aaAAhh​ ​​
​​​ ​wUUH​ ​​
​​​ ​AAAUH​ ​​
​​​ ​auAAAUGH​ ​​
​​​ ​wuh...​ ​​
​​​ ​Now, speak.​ ​​
​​​ ​Where is the anime location?​ ​​
​​​ ​Vhere is it?​ ​​
​​​ ​It is simp–​ ​​
​​​ ​LOOK!​ ​​
​​​ ​?​ ​​
​​ ​LOOK!​ ​​
​​​ ​sssex​ :)​ ​​
​​​ ​Do you think this is​ ​​
​​ ​where they keep the anime?​ ​​
​​​ ​Most certainly.​ ​​
​​​ ​Perhaps.​ ​​
​​​ ​[bonk]​ ​​
​​​ ​Access denied.​ ​​
​​​ ​Please validate​ ​​
​​​ ​that​ ​​
​​​ ​that you​ ​​
​​​ ​that you are​ ​​
​​​ ​that you are hu-man.​ ​​
​​​ ​Both?​ ​​
​​​ ​Both.​ ​​
​​ ​Both?​ ​​
​​ ​Both.​ ​​
​​​ ​Both.​ ​​
​​​ ​Both is good!​ ​​
​​​ ​[error]​ ​​
​​​ ​[gun clicks]​ ​​
​​​ ​[:pensive:]​ ​​
​​​ ​oohh?​ ​​
​​​ ​o​ ​​
​​​ ​ouf​ ​​
​​​ ​[flick]​ ​​
​​​ ​Hey buddy, you picked the wrong door.​ ​​
​​​ ​The Weeb Club's two blocks down!​ ​​
​​​ ​Two blocks?​ ​​
​​​ ​Veerry good!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yus!​ ​​
​​ ​Veerry good!​ ​​
​​​ ​Thanks, king!​ ​​
​​​ ​We GO​ ​​
​​​ ​[no]​ ​​
​​​ ​Now I'll show you who's​ ​​
​​ ​boss of ​this facility!​ ​​
​​​ ​[blip]​ ​​
​​​ ​Where did he go?​ ​​
​​​ ​GAAAAAAAH​ ​​
​​​ ​YAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA​ ​​
​​​ ​You are going down, you Sputnik!​ ​​
​​​ ​What?​ ​​
​​​ ​aaaAAAAAA​ ​​
​​​ ​AAAAAAaaa​ ​​
​​​ ​[radio chatter]​ ​​
​​​ ​ohh...!​ ​​
​​​ ​[PANIC]​ ​​
​​​ ​aa​ ​​
​​​ ​aA​ ​​
​​​ ​[the eagle has landed]​ ​​
​​​ ​[indistinct radio chatter]​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm going to step off the LM now.​ ​​
​​​ ​That's one small step for man...​ ​​
​​​ ​[oeuf]​ ​​
​​​ ​[muffled]​ ​​
​​​ ​[vineboom.mp3]​ ​​
​​​ ​oOOOhh my GAAAaad​ ​​
​​​ ​[crash]​ ​​
​​​ ​[bam]​ ​​
​​​ ​[yes]​ ​​
​​​ ​[no]​ ​​
​​​ ​[explode]​ ​​
​​​ ​OHHHHHHH​ ​​
​​ ​NOOOOOOOO​ ​​
​​​ ​Your friend is dead!​ ​​
​​​ ​EEEHHHHH​ ​​
​​​ ​UWAAAAAAA​ ​​
​​​ ​And now it's YOUR turn!​ ​​
​​​ ​[reverse no]​ ​​
​​​ ​What...?​ ​​
​​ ​[reverse no]​ ​​
​​​ ​Fly me to the moon​ ​​
​​​ ​And let me play among the stars​ ​​
​​​ ​Let me see what Spring is like​ ​​
​​​ ​On Jupiter and Mars​ ​​
​​​ ​[blamo]​ ​​
​​​ ​DAAH!​ ​​
​​​ ​you got blood on this​ ​​
​​​ ​you got BLOOD on this​ ​​
​​​ ​sandvich​ ​​
​​​ ​Wat?​ ​​
​​​ ​umf​ ​​
​​​ ​[no]​ ​​
​​​ ​[NieR Automata OST - Kain ( Salvation )]​ ​​
​​​ ​It is sad day...​ ​​
​​​ ​Da-a...​ ​​
​​ ​(Yes...)​ ​​
​​​ ​Enough is enough!​ ​​
​​​ ​I've had it with these​ ​​
​​ ​mother####ing WEEBS​ ​​
​​​ ​on this mother####ing​ ​​
​​ ​MILITARY BASE​ ​​
​​​ ​[top 10 most satisfying anime deaths]​ ​​
​​​ ​[boop]​ ​​
​​​ ​[boom]​ ​​
​​​ ​hmmm?​ ​​
​​​ ​OOOOOOOOOOO​ ​​
​​​ ​[triumph]​ ​​
​​​ ​What now?​ ​​
​​​ ​[Sex-man]​ ​​
​​​ ​Aaaahh...​ ​​
​​​ ​Tea-for-Two "Heavy Weapons" Guy...​ ​​
​​​ ​You may not go any further...​ ​​
​​​ ​My employers have grown​ ​​
​​ ​rather fond of their...​ ​​
​​​ ​anime... girls​ ​​
​​​ ​And, well I–​ ​​
​​​ ​[vrooooom]​ ​​
​​ ​And, well I–​ ​​
​​​ ​Uh...​ ​​
​​ ​[vrooooom]​ ​​
​​​ ​W-Wait!​ ​​
​​​ ​Very nice!​ ​​
​​​ ​'6'​ ​​
​​​ ​'69'​ ​​
​​​ ​'694'​ ​​
​​​ ​'6942'​ ​​
​​​ ​'69420-S'​ ​​
​​​ ​'69420-SEX'​ ​​
​​​ ​[phone vibrates]​ ​​
​​​ ​Yes?​ ​​
​​​ ​Hi, ceno0.​ ​​
​​​ ​This camera angle is s###.​ ​​
​​​ ​Wut?​ ​​
​​​ ​[vineboom.mp3]​ ​​
​​​ ​AA​ ​​
​​ ​[vineboom.mp3]​ ​​
​​​ ​I need you to take better camera angle.​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay!​ ​​
​​​ ​No.​ ​​
​​​ ​Boring.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah,​ ​​
​​​ ​that will do.​ ​​
​​​ ​'8'​ ​​
​​​ ​'8936'​ ​​
​​​ ​'893617'​ ​​
​​​ ​mmMMMMMM​ ​​
​​​ ​ooOOOOOIII​ ​​
​​​ ​aaaAAAAAHH​ ​​
​​​ ​AAAAAAA​ ​​
​​​ ​A̸̼͇͌͘G̴̠͗G̴͈̜̃̉H̵̨͐H̴̡͍͊̚H̴̪̀͘H̸̯͋H̷̜̤͝H̶̻͌̕͜H̷̳̽H̷̢̯̔̈́​ ​​
​​​ ​Ȧ̴ͅA̵̤͝R̶͙̀R̷̲͑R̵̠̐R̵̙͛R̶̹͑Ğ̶͙G̸̪͑G̵͚̚H̶̱͂H̴̡́H̸̞́Ḫ̶̈́​ ​​
​​​ ​alright​ ​​
​​​ ​Sex...​ ​​
​​​ ​NNOW​ ​​
​​​ ​[death]​ ​​
​​​ ​:(​ ​​
​​​ ​[it is very sad day]​ ​​
​​​ ​[jk]​ ​​
​​​ ​sex... :)​ ​​
​​​ ​NNNOWWWWW​ ​​
​​​ ​(alright, what the hell is this?)​ ​​
​​ ​так але я не понял это че​ ​​
​​​ ​AAAAAGHHHH​ ​​
​​​ ​(alright, what the hell is this?)​ ​​
​​ ​так але я не понял это че​ ​​
​​​ ​[English CC made by ​DinoBoi]​ ​​
​​​ ​[There's more at the end!]​ ​​
​​​ ​I had to run away from here​ ​​
​​​ ​Before the storm hit​ ​​
​​​ ​We see eye to eye​ ​​
​​​ ​I told me without you​ ​​
​​​ ​We've got only one sky​ ​​
​​​ ​Blue, red, and black paranoia​ ​​
​​​ ​What is it like to you?​ ​​
​​​ ​(Like to you?)​ ​​
​​ ​What is it like to you?​ ​​
​​​ ​No one can see the colors but you​ ​​
​​​ ​We've got only one sky​ ​​
​​​ ​Joy, grief, wild paranoia​ ​​
​​​ ​What is it like to you?​ ​​
​​​ ​No one can see the colors, the colors​ ​​
​​​ ​But you​ ​​
​​​ ​Wat?​ ​​
​​​ ​aUUUUAGAHH​ ​​
​