[grunting noises]
[angry babbling]
SEAL IT UP! SEAL IT UP!
GUYS?! WHAT HAPPENED?
Golf Ball [narrating]: We were trying
to cure Barf Bag after she collapsed...
[chattering, yelling frantically]
People, PEOPLE! We are working as HARD as we CAN!
After Barf Bag's vomit poured out last episode,
being empty has caused her
to be...sicker than usual!
Her BARF MOLECULES must be required
for a healthy and happy bag!
Tennis Ball [narrating]: With Rocky
gone, the only way to get vomit are
the remains left lava-fied in the volcano, or
to simply destroy Barf Bag and recover her!
NO, you can't despawn her, PLEASE
try the lava...vomit stuff first.
Golf Ball [narrating]: So we tried
the lava-infused vomit but...
Tennis Ball [narrating]:
Something was immediately wrong...
Tennis Ball [narrating]: Different
liquids seem to influence Barf Bag
but this unhealthy mixture seemed...DEADLY.
BRO! You ok? Nap inside at
least, don't do it here--
BLARGHH!
WHAT?!
EVERYONE, RUN FOR YOUR LIVES!
GET TO COVER AND STAY SAFE!
[screaming]
ARE YOU OKAY, TEAM8S! GET IN HERE!
SORRY TD!! You might be CONTAMINATED! Get to
cover and avoid those guys as FAST as POSSIBLE!
[glass shattering]
Wait--I’M SOR--
[slap]
OW!
GRRRR!
What’s the happs? Climbing
through broken glass?! I AM IN!
NO! WE NEED BOARDS NOW! NO! WE NEED NAILS NOW!
Nails? Boards? Or did you mean to say…Caaaake?
♪ Hey Two! ♪
♪ When you bake a cake ♪
♪ Decorate and--
Tennis Ball: TWO, the UNDEAD are TRYING
TO GET INSIDE! We are in a serious rush!
My song…the only thing undead
right now is my spirits.
You guys really could’ve let me finish that song.
FINE!
♪ take it to the players who are safe ♪
♪ That's how you know it's Cake at Sta-a-ake ♪
♪ Cake at Stake ♪
[angry babbling]
SEAL IT UP! SEAL IT UP!
GUYS?! WHAT HAPPENED?
TWO! We need more boards and nails A-S-A-P!
Well good thing you’re all
assembled! Are You Okay,
it’s time for your ceremony first! Today’s
Cakes are planks of wood and some nails!
Two: ERASER! TV! You’re both safe
with 6383 and 6365 votes respectively!
These steaks should have Pen’s name CARVED
right in! Because he got 6336 votes!
Gimme that!
Eraser: More windows covered
the better! Mush, TB, mush!
Next safe is Tennis Ball with
6335 votes!...Wow these are close!
WELL DESERVED TENNI--wait…I’M IN THE BOTTOM TWO?!
Tennis Ball: NO! Golfy, you can’t go!
Shucks…I think it’s one of us, Puffball!
And right after I understood your value!
WAAAAAAH!
Hey, well…if our journey ends here, I’m
just glad we reached some common ground,
Golf Ball. I just wanted people
to acknowledge ME! So I think--
[glass shattering]
AAHH-OWW!
SORRY GUYS!
NOOOO! I’M SO SORRY, PUFFBALL! WE’LL
SORT THIS OUT! TWO! Who is safe?!
By a THREE VOTE DIFFERENCE…
Puffball is out with 6311 votes. Golf
Ball, you survive with 6314 votes.
Poor Puffball. We’ll avenge you, “Are You Okay”er!
[rumblings]
HURRY TWO, GIVE US OUR CAKES, WE NEED TO SORT--
[knocking]
Anchor: GUYS! It’s me, Anchor! Let me in!
Wh--is that one of the roof guys?
Reckon those sick folks got to him already?
Anchor: NO, they’re biting people but I
escaped! But they’ll probably be back,
please, let me in, please!
So, uh…who wants to open that door?
Maybe your wooden steak cake
might change your mind? Donut,
Gaty, anyone brave since you’re both safe
with 6388 and 5686 votes respectively?
Noo--ARGGH!
Gotta learn to catch with your legs, Donut!
I’ve got it! How about whichever one of us gets
the least votes has to let the reject inside?
PIN! What if it’s YOU?!
We always do so well!
[slow-mo]: We’ll be FINE, Coiny!
And Barf Bag is safe! I’ll send
her some wood and some nails!
Discy: NO! NO!
Conch Shell: HELP!
WHY DID YOU DO THAT? NOW SHE
CAN SMASH THE DOOR DOWN EASIER!
SORRYSORRYSORRYSORRYSORRYSORRY--
Pin is safe with 4917 votes!
Needle: No! NO! No! NO! No! NO! I can’t!
Coiny: PIN, PIN, PIN!
Needle: I CAN’T! I can’t! I CAN’T! AH! AH! AH!
Coiny: PIN, PIN, PIN! DANGER! DANGER! DANGER!
With a TWENTY VOTE DIFFERENCE--one of
you is leaving the game and opening
that door for Anchor…and that contestant is
Coiny,
who is out with 4870 votes! Needle
narrowly survives with 4890 votes.
COINY--NO! I’m so…I'M SO SORRY!
[deep inhale] It’s fine…I’m just
letting Anchor in…it’ll be okay---
Not just about the door, Coiny!
You’re out of the game and…I’m
sorry. I wanted to go further with
you. How can I do this without you?
[gasp]
GAH! COINY! NOOOOOO!
ARE YOU OKAY! Upstairs NOW, we have to GO!
NOOTTT YOU, TEARDROP! NOT AFTER LAST TIME!
[slapping]
ERASER, cut out these SHENANIGANS this INSTANT!
Both of YOU, UP HERE NOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOW!
♪
Those dead guys are SPREADING!
Where’s everyone else?
[snap]
TPOTers! Where are you all?
HERE to protect our fellow PACT member!
Bell is SOARING through the skies!
Basketball: Well…soaring might be a stretch…
[cutting out]: We’re--stake--at the---
Those chumps gotta be at the
Steakhouse. Pen and I love
eating scraps in there but the reception sucks!
YEP, they’re in there alright!
They’ve locked us out! HELLO?!
Everyone for themselves! Here,
we’ll take the Steakhouse,
and you'll take some old steaks! Not
all…we gotta keep some of them. Sound fair?
STEAKS?! YaAaAaAaY!
WE’RE GONNA FIND FOUR AND X!
We’re in trouble, Two! We
can’t hold them off forever!
Guys, you all have to STAY SAFE! In fact,
that’s TODAY’S CHALLENGE! Simply SURVIVE!
The two teams to be completely wiped
out first will be up for elimination,
OR if there AREN’T two teams who go extinct,
whoever loses the MOST members will lose. GO!
That’s assuming there’s even
a SOLUTION to this MADNESS!
Two: JUST NOT! Did you guys get all of that?
[cutting out]: Did… all that?
WAIT--SAY IT ONE MORE TIME! WHAT?!
[cutting out]: Today’s challenge…two
teams…completely wiped out!
Completely wipe our team out? Got it!
Fun.
Beep! Beep! Beep!
As for us, I’m pretty sure I should be immune
to this stuff. How can I become a sickly green?
I’m ALREADY green! I LOVE my way of thinking!
So let’s just hunker down here, and we’ll--
Two! NO! GO BACK TO NORMAL, WE NEED YOU!
FOUR’S POWER is probably strong
enough to fix these guys!
Donut, QUICK!
HELP, YOU TWO! HEEELP!
What the---”Kitchen Bonding
Retreat, be back soon”--WHAT?!
Found anything yet, Clock?
[sigh] You know I did, Four…
Play along, please!
Ugh...
YAAAY! Youuuu caught me!
BEST. DAY. EVER!
YAAAAAY!
Yaaaay.
Needle: I can’t hold them off forever!
C’mon, there’s a Basement
through that door, let’s go!
Golf Ball [from upstairs]: Two!
NO! Go back to normal, WE NEED YOU!
[gasp] TWO’S IN TROUBLE?
Go, GO! I have to help Two!
GATY! NO! We’re losing everybody!
[loud banging]
WHAT was THAT?!
BLARRGGHHH!
COINY?! Guys, we can still save hi--
Pin, NO! Coiny is NOT COINY RIGHT NOW!
You’ll thank me later, hold on tight!
NO! NO!
[screaming]
[splash]
Those…THINGS are approaching!
Just let us IN you JUST NOTTERS!
Okay…I can show you guys something,
but you HAVE to keep it a secret!
CLOUDY’S COLLECTION! This is
where it’s been since he got out?
He’s VERY protective of it,
so please be as gentle as--
[rustling]
GO, GO, GO!
Pfffeeee--YEW! Good idea, Yellow Face!
The collection has grown so SO large
with donations from my factory,
should take AGES for those guys to break in!
STEAK TIIIIME!
NOM. MmmMH MHMHM! DE-LISH!
You guys…SO heavy…NO…YOU DON’T THINK…UNDEAD
NON-EXISTY IS PULLING US DOWN, DO YOU?
It’s CLEARLY Yoyleball down there, so
GET HIM OFF before we all die, dingaling!
She’s…augh--RIGHT SNOWBALL! You
might need to jump off, I’m sorry!
WHAT?! Those freak WIMPS are RIGHT BEHIND US!
You’re METAL!
Yeah they…ughh…probably can’t even bite you!
FINE!
[sigh] Thank you, Snowball! Muuuuuch better!
Oh, phew! See, I knew they couldn’t do anythi--
SNOWBALL! I’M SO SORRY!
GO, BELL! GO, GO, GO!
Hmm, looks like a crowd are
chasing Bell over there…
GAH! THEY’RE COMING THIS WAY! BLACK
HOLE, YOU MUST STOP THEM! NOW!
Black Hole: As in--
SUCK THEM UP!!!
Black Hole: But they’re not DEAD,
they’re…UNDEAD. I…uh, I don’t think I can…
Phew, you can’t argue now, huh Buddy? Well,
I have a solution! We simply MOVE Tree!
That’s ludicrous, have you SEEN how huge he is
right now? How are we possibly going to do that?
[splash]
Marker: Do you have a BETTER
IDEA?! Quick, FANNY! DIG, DIG, DIG!
[splash]
Look, the reception was bad, the--the challenge
can’t POSSIBLY be to kill each-other, right?
[electricity crackling]
Guys? HELLO?!
We can talk about this! We
can figure something out…
[bang]
HELLO? What was that?
I saw that…anyone there?
Gelatin [recording]: WELCOME TO
GELATIN’S STAKEHOUSE! If you're
looking for my house MADE of
steak, it's across the street.
Pst…over here, buddy.
The stress of all of this was JUST
TOO MUCH for Little ol’ Nickely-loo!
I figure we can just SLEEP THROUGH IT!
I found this bed in the trash, and
I’m all snug up with this blanket!
And now all I need to make
this complete would be…A-HAH!
I found a nice little pillow! Oh
OH so COMFY! Yay, this is so comf--
WAIT--PILLOW?!
Nickel: aUUUGg…
One down! Hello, Book!
I could really use some of
your glue for some nice armor!
PILLOW! NO! PILLLLOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOW!
Run…Run RUN RUN RUN RUN!
[scream]
OOW! What happened to--
--OH MY FENCE!
WE’RE STUCK! PEEPS IN BOTH DIRECTIONS!
TWO! I’M COMING!
Split up, SPLIT UP! TB, we need the lab!
WE NEED TO THINK OF SOMETHING FAST!
TV: We’ll try to lead the undead elsewhere!
WHOOPS! I meant to hit TD, hahaha!
TV: If we stack up, we can access the vents
up there, for escape! You two, get on my head!
TV: WARNING! WARNING! THEY ARE COMING!
Eraser: Hurry, TD! We gotta jump!
Alrighty, TV, grab my legs--
[fallen soldier sirens]
TV: Good luck, my friends. May we meet again.
Wha--NO--TV, we can--
NOO! Teardrop, help me up, please!
Teardrop? TEAARRDROP?! DON’T DO THIS!
CURSE YOU TEARDRO--
---Oh?
Thank you, TD. We got this--
[munch]
Auug---ohh…
YOU GUYS GOTTA HURRY! THEY’RE ON THEIR WAY!
Maybe--uh, I can find some protection?
Where are they…
Woah! So many goodies! But what are they after?
BLACK HOLE SILLY! Don’t suck US up, hehe!
OH! Of course not! But--guys! I need
this stash! I need to protect Tree!
WAIT--if you take the whole
collection, we are all going to DIE!
BAH--but if I DON’T take them,
TREE is going to DIE! Why are they so
adamantly coming to you guys, anyway?
Who knows, but these steaks are getting co-OLD!
So to you, little cold steak, I say: GOODBYE!
USE THOSE STEAKS TO DEFLECT! I’m
taking this stash to save Tree!
Where are they CHASING US?
Maybe they’d STOP and GIVE
UP if you’d just GO HIGHER!
I could go higher if you all GOT OFF!
WOAH, SICK! This team’s
lame, I’m joining those guys!
[biting]
Not working, STUPID! But it doesn’t
matter, I like you guys, for now!
ARGH! I TOLD YOU, BELL! She’s a
COMPLETE LIABILITY, RIGHT NOW!
He’s getting bigger! Just fly, FLY!
The lava combined with the Barf
seems to have caused Barf Bag’s
insides to rot! This mutation seems
to spread when she bites people…
So if we can undo the rotting…maybe
by powering the bodies up somehow,
maybe we can get Barf Bag and
everyone else back to normal!
Argh…if only we knew what caused Barf
Bag to get so strong last episode…
Two?
Two [whispering]: Over here.
Two? Are you okay?
Two [whispering]: In here. Come on.
Uh, Two, I’m…a little freaked out.
Two [whispering]: Inside.
[breathing heavily] Two…I--I know
you’re…not you right now but…
Two [whispering]: C’mon.
[breathes out] Two…
You there?
TWO?
Gaty: Is that--are you okay?
[whispering] Two--are you okay?
Gaty: WAIT, TWO, DON’T--
Hey guys, what should we do when
we start running low on steaks?
I don’t know, maybe just yell
“warning” or something to let us know--
WARNING, WARNING, WARNING! We
have ONE steaky left, team!
I need a BIG stash, guys! Keep throwing!
[breathing in and out quickly]
We’re doomed…they’re coming!
We have one steak left…who is brave
enough to head off with it and save us?
Not me!
I WANT REVENGE!
oOF!
[gasping for air] ARE YOU GUYS OKAY?!
Price-Tag: Hello?
Price-Tag? Is that you?
What the sales catalogue are
you guys doing down there?
The sewers led us here! Where are you right now?
Price-Tag: I’m hiding in
the back of the steakhouse,
did you guys know this used to be a shadeshouse?
Those shades are handy! Some
change colours and stuff,
should be good for looking for those
dead guys and keeping everyone alive!
DONUT?!
Wait…”keeping everyone alive”...
Guys! The challenge is to stay
ALIVE…we don’t have to hurt each-other!
GUYS! …ARGH, FINE! “Night
vision”, eh? Should be handy…
Dum dee dum, do, do, do…
PILLOW! We need to STAY ALIVE! DON’T DO THIS!
STOOOOP!
OoooooOO!
Aw, fluff.
[slowly breathing heavily]
Bomby? Nickel? Any of you safe? Pillow’s dead…
Bomby: Good work, Price-Tag! Pillow
is a tough foe, good job on--
[rip]
They only grazed me. And now, Bomby, there’s you.
Bomby: And now there’s you.
OMIGOSHOMIGOSHOMIGOSHOMIGOSH--
GETTING THERE! We need more time, Black Hole!
Check THIS out!
STAY BACK!
Haha, look, it’s working!
[splash]
NO!
They’re CLIMBING! Dig, Marker! Dig!
NO! I can’t believe this is our end, AND they
got Icy! Waaaaah, I wish we could’ve saved Icy!
Waaaah, I wish I could’ve
sold more from my factory!
I mean, uh…what Bottle said!
GAH! None of the gadgets in
this STUPID factory work!
I can’t believe there’s something that
the two of us can’t figure out!
I know.
GAH!
This is all YOUR FAULT Barf Bag!
[sharp inhale]
Uh…hey guys…where am I?
BARF BAG? YOU’RE BACK TO NORMAL?
OH MY GOSH…TD! IT WAS YOU! Your effects on Barf
Bag’s lava barf somehow made it less degenerative…
But unlike Barf Bag, most of
the undead victims don’t have
external innards. We need to find
another way to cure everyone else!
They’re going to have to ingest the barf
somehow…Barf Bag, you are the only way we
can save everyone. We’re gonna have
to take your innards out once again.
Uh, I still don’t know what’s happening. But
if it helps everyone else, let’s do it lol.
There’s not…there’s not enough in here, we need
more liquid! Teardrop, can you hop back in?
But…if she gets absorbed…she’ll die!
And get…eliminated…oh…
Thank you, TD! Your sacrifice won’t be in vain!
Barf Bag and Teardrop, you are
HEROES! Hurry TB, let’s feed this to--
AHHHH!
BELL, WE GOTTA HIDE SOMEWHERE!
I’ll take us back to the grasslands--maybe
they’ve sorted something out, already!
THEY’RE GONE! WE’RE SAFE!
WATER! WE NEED TO GET OUT OF HERE NOW!
There’s a crack forming above! Let’s escape!
I think we’re doomed!
This stash is HUGE, it’s gonna take
forever to climb over! Have faith!
GUYS?! Any updates? Have
you solved these guys yet?
No we--wait--WHAT IS THAT?
WATCH OUT!!!!
GO GO GO!
Pin: NEEDLE! NO!
TWO, NOO!!!
Hi. I’m not Two though.
W--Gaty, you’re here too? Where are we?
It appears Two sent us to the
elimination space instead of
killing us like all of those other undead guys.
[sigh of relief] Even in
zombie form, Two’s pretty cool.
So…can I rejoin?
NO!
[glass shattering]
Huh? A drink for my final moments? Bottoms up!
GLUG GLUG!
BLERGH! Reminds me of
ROCKY-OL-BUDDY! Have this, Conch-man!
W--oh! Hey guys!
WOAH! That made him BACK TO NORMAL! IT WORKS!
Have YOU ever needed to get this vial to the OTHER
DEAD GUYS? Then why not COOK IT into some STEAKS?
Good idea! But how do we get
in? We’re still locked out!
Hello Bomby!
Should we do this…the easy way?
Or the other easy way?
The even easier way! I’m gonna
take YOU down on my terms.
Huh?
Oh no, I just lit my fuse.
Wait--Don’t--
[explosion]
WHAT? FIRE? FIREE?!!?
OUCH! BLACK HOLE, STOP THAT
SNOWBALL! IT NEARLY KILLED ME!
YOU GOT IT!
GUYS! Get in the kitchen!
HHMMM! Have YOU ever wanted
to solve an apocalypse?
I think we’re safe for now, no more pulling, Tree!
Luckily we caused nooooo death
whatsoever! And no danger, too! Hahaha!
No--OPEN UP AGAIN! WHY IS IT CLOSED?!
Ugh, my roots are getting itchy.
Probably because of all of
our digging. Sorry, Tree.
OPEN! OPEN!
I can’t do it…
COINY--I’m so sorry you got out…I don’t
even know if I can figure this out alone--
GARRGH!
NO--NEEDLE WAS RIGHT. Right now, you’re
not you. But I can figure this out!
[banging]
GOSH! I DID IT! I did it.
Oh, hey Pi--uh…WAH? Did you KILL COINY?
Uh…it’s not what it looks like?
[gulp] H--huh? What happened?
[licking noises] MhmHHMMM!
YAY! You guys--you did it!
I don’t know what’s with all this snow, but the
steakhouse looks nice! Let’s snap you all back!
[snaps fingers]
PIN! You also survived!
I’m so happy to see you, Gaty! That was
honestly rough, today. Seeing Coiny like that.
Yeah. I saw the same thing in Two.
But…I saw a good side of them,
as well. Even when they were…like that.
Two could’ve killed us but…they didn’t.
It’s just nice to hold onto that.
I really didn’t think I could
play this game without Coiny,
but…he kinda…pushed me towards
fighting for myself down there.
Yeah…I think that’s a good way
to look at it. Thanks Gaty.
Pen bit me. Got a good bite
too! I screamed and it hurt.
We were, uh…talking about the good qualities
we saw in our friends, even when zombified.
Me too, haha. Classic Pen.
Always biting something.
Golf Ball: I thought you KILLED us,
Two! But we just went where Pie was!
Oh, I sent you guys THERE? Whoops…you weren’t
meant to go there, yet. Oh well! Glad you’re safe!
But let’s see how many members you all have left!
Up first, TEARDROP!
Wait…Teardrop…died.
[gasp]
Teardrop…I’m sorry to say that you are eliminated.
Hey, TD--I know we’ve had our ups and downs
but…I really appreciate you
trying to save me back there.
And honestly, do you even NEED to
win the power of two? Look at all
the amazing things you’ve pulled off this season.
You played a great game, TD.
And the best man won, hahaha.
Hahaha, get out of here!
Bye Teardrop.
BUT YOU’RE NOT OFF THE HOOK JUST
YET, FOLKS! Because TWO TEAMS lose,
remember! Let’s see which of you guys either got
completely wiped out, or lost the most members!
DEATH P.A.C.T. Again, you still
have all four members remaining!
The S!, you lost one member, losing Ice Cube!
The Strongest Team on Earth, you lost one
member as Snowball died mid-challenge!
Are You Okay lost THREE members,
as Pen, Eraser and TV all died!
Team8s, you lost three members as Barf
Bag, Donut and Needle all passed away.
And Just Not…none of you are even here.
Because your WHOLE TEAM got wiped out.
So Just Not, your team is up for elimination!
Oh, I guess I’ll fill in for
them. Nooooooo, or whatever.
VIEWERS! “JUST NOT” is up for
elimination! You only get ONE VOTE TOTAL,
so, vote for one of them to stay in
the game! Make your one vote count!
♪ I have a Pen, I have a Bubble (new plush!) ♪
♪ Uh! Bubble-Pen! ♪
♪ I have a Pin (new plush too!), I
have Gray Bubble (Adam's plush) ♪
♪ Uh! Gray-Bubble-Pin! ♪
♪ Bubble-Pen, Gray-Bubble-Pin ♪
♪ Uh! Pin-Gray-Bubble-Bubble-Pen ♪
If you liked that musical performance, which I know you did,
then you can buy these plushies for Christmas
on the store online, 'cause they're still up there!
And thank you for watching this episode of TPOT 9, with zombies,
and I'll see you in TPOT 10!
Oh also! TWOW Season 2 sign-ups are open right now.
Join if you wanna compete with me!
WHERE. DID EVERYONE. GO?!
WHERE DID THEY GO?!
WHERE. DID. THEY. GOOOOoOoOooO!
[everyone arguing]
We HAVE to go up THERE!
Further into the forest! INTO the forest!
We should go BACK to the SCHOOL!
Blah blah blah blah
STOOOOOOOP! I’m just gonna LEAVE
if you ALL. KEEP. FIGHTING!
I like that!
WHAT?
No, like, groups! If we split up
and find a way out, we can regroup!
Pencil: LIY, why don’t you go do the
waterfall with Stapy and uh…Match!
B--BUT! We HAVE TO LIKE STICK TOGETHER!
MATCHY, just CALM DOWN! We
can hang out all the time
once we escape! But those guys need you, now go!
A new adventure awaits! Let’s go!
Pencil: Firey Jr.! Head deep into the forest,
and take 8-Ball and Dora with you!
David, Bracelety, I think those
classrooms are our way out! Let’s go!
Aw!
What?
I think he’s upset we couldn’t save Roboty!
I mean…we can check the classroom
on the way, might still be there.
YOU!
BAD IDEA, RUN!
GRRRR!
IN HERE! RIGHT NOW!
[slam]
Weird…
Oooh!
Huh?
Pencil: Th-there are other numbers?
[rumbling, cracking]
Hey guys!